[{"answer": "Well, Wolf, what we're hearing here from government officials is that they have started an investigation into this incident to try and figure out what happened.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "What is the latest in Libya?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, Wolf, what's going on is we have a hundred -- a few hundred protesters and the police battling it out.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "What is going on in Cairo?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, I think the United States is already playing a role in sending FBI forces to help investigate, find out who was responsible.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "What does it say to you?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "At least 20.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "For how many years have you known him?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "And he worked hard to get rid of Gadhafi through these rebels?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "I think he'd say not -- do not waiver, that the United States was on a course to try to help facilitate a very traumatic transition in many of these countries.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "What would he want the United States to do towards Libya in the aftermath of what has happened, this tragic killing of him and three of his colleagues?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Short answer is, Wolf, we don't know enough yet.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Does this look, I mean these two events, in Cairo, storming of the U.S. embassy, in Benghazi, the U.S. diplomatic epic (ph) mission there, storming on the 11th anniversary of 9/11, does it look like, A, these were coordinated, and do you feel it has the fingerprints of some sort of al Qaeda-related organization out there?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "I'm not getting into politics, Wolf.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Is that what you're saying?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Well, it looks like extremists may have been involved in the attack in Benghazi.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Do you believe al Qaeda had a role in this one way or another, Robin?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I'll let the American people judge that.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Do you think it was irresponsible?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "I think the point that he made is almost a self-evident one.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "What do you say?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "That's what it looks like, but I mean you come into an American embassy, American soil, American sovereign territory, and you slaughter our ambassador, that's an act of war against the United States of America.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Was this an al Qaeda operation?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "I don't think we know yet and, you know, whether John Kerry is right or not about that, for Romney to come -- it's just not effective and one of the things we learned as reporters is the first information is often wrong, and you have to let things settle out and Romney doesn't have the lead in foreign policy in the campaign now so it probably is better if he is restrained and let the facts develop and then develop support or critique.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "What do you make of this angry exchange that has developed?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Well, it's just not effective because -- it's about one statement and whether, you know, the White House changes its position, the State Department does, many times it's a volatile situation.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Smart politics, not-so smart politics?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Well, we just don't know because there are back channel communications, obviously there is not a great deal of love between Obama and Netanyahu, or at least it looks like there's not.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Big deal, little deal, how do you see this?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, look, if you -- and they talk about this in the White House.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Who was -- there is plenty of blame to throw around for the downgrading of the U.S. credit rating which was significant, but who deserves more of that blame?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Well, I -- you know, you go through and I go through in microscopic detail the meetings and the phone calls and so forth.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Why couldn't he work his will like other presidents, like Reagan or Bill Clinton?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Well, it's not about golf, it's about personal relations.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Is that an issue really?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Well, that's a great question and people are going to have to make their judgment of it.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "If he's re-elected will he do a better job in this town over the next four years?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Yes, what I say is there's responsibility on both heads, but presidential leadership matters.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Do you want to tell us what you say?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Well, thank you, Wolf.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "What's going on over here?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "My personal opinion is this was a mistake by Governor Romney, who frequently has very good judgment.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Is this appropriate?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Well, unfortunately, I think we all are mourning the loss and we should be.", "docId": "120912pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Should the President have gone out and started campaigning even as all of us are mourning the loss of these Americans?", "qSentId": 443}]